http://www.tracks.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy PolicyTracks Ltd. are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of all our customers and clients. Please read the following policy carefully in order to understand how your data will be processed and used.1) We may collect personal data from you in the following ways:
(a) Information provided by filling in forms on our website www.tracks.co.uk including data provided by you when ordering from our website and subscribing to our mailing list.
(b) Recording correspondence sent to and received from you by email, telephone, letter and on social media (via our Facebook page and Twitter account).
(c) Details of transactions relating to Tracks Ltd.
(d) Recording your visits to our website and how you use it including location data and traffic data.2) We may collect information regarding the following:
(a) Your operating system, IP address and browser type, however none of this information can be used to identify any individual.
(b) In order to help us improve our website and service we may use cookies to access the information (relating to Tracks Ltd) which is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us to recognise you when you return to our website and to store information about your preferences when using our website. They cannot be used to access anything other than information about Tracks Ltd. You are able to refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your internet browser, however this may affect your access to certain parts of our website.3) We use information held about you in the following ways:
(a) To provide you with products, services or information that you request from us or that we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
(b) To notify you about changes to our services.
(c) To ensure that we carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. For example, we will pass your contact details to our courier companies in order to ensure the correct and efficient delivery of your order.
(d) To ensure that content on our website is presented in the most effective manner.4) The data which we collect from you may be transferred and stored at a destination outside the EEA (European Economic Area). By using our website and consequently submitting your data you agree to this transfer. Tracks Ltd takes all steps to ensure that your data is stored and treated securely in accordance with the terms set out in this Privacy Policy and in compliance with the relevant data protection laws including the GDPR5) We may collect the following information through our online purchasing system:
(a) Your name, billing address, shipping address (if different), telephone number and email address.
(b) Information relating to your credit card.
All your account information is accessible by you at the Tracks Ltd website using the unique Username and Password you created when you set-up your online account. Your log-in details, credit card information and IP address are encrypted and stored in a secure database with limited access to Tracks Ltd. employees only.6) None of the information collected by Tracks Ltd will be disclosed to third parties except in the following circumstances:
(a) Contact information provided to the courier companies in order to deliver your order.
(b) Order details provided to third party suppliers who manage the secure payment platform and credit card processing service in order for them to carry out the transactions.
(c) If we are required to do so by a valid Court Order or lawfully requested by government or law enforcement authorities.
(d) If it becomes necessary to protect the rights or property of Tracks Ltd.7) You have the following rights regarding the personal data we hold:
(a) You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you, in electronic format, free of charge.
(b) You have the right to correct any data that we hold about you that is either incomplete or inaccurate.
(c) You have the right to ask for your data to be erased from our records, in accordance with article 17 of the GDPR.
(d) You have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation.8) The personal data we collect from you when purchasing goods or entering other transactional agreements is necessary for the fulfilment of our contract with you. All other personal data is processed for our legitimate interests (as set out below) and to comply with our legal obligations:
(a) Selling and supplying goods and services to our customers
(b) Promoting, marketing and advertising our services and products
(c) Sending promotional communication which is relevant and tailored to customer needs and requirements.
(d) Handling customer queries and complaints.
(e) Preventing fraud.9) We will only retain your personal data for as long as is necessary to fulfil our contract with you, including satisfying accounting and legal requirements. Tracks Ltd retains customer details and transaction history for 7 years in order to meet these requirements.10) Tracks Ltd will not send you emails asking you to provide account or log-in information. If you receive any suspicious emails regarding your Tracks Ltd account or activity please contact us. Please remember to keep your log-in details a secret and do not give out any personal or account information to third parties. Please also ensure that when you have ended your session on the Tracks Ltd. website you logout of your account and close your internet browser window.Any changes we make to this privacy policy will be posted on this page.If you have any concerns or questions about anything mentioned in the above policy or in relation to your personal date please email us at sales@tracks.co.uk or write to us at Tracks Ltd, 17 St Georges Street, Chorley, Lancashire, PR7 2AA. Company Reg: 03149774. VAT number 885097574.This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.AcceptReject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.Translate »
No products in the basket.
Beatles MemorabiliaBeatles MemorabiliaApple MemorabiliaApple AcetatesBeatles & Solo Rare RecordsBeatles & Solo RecordsBeatles Fan Club ItemsBeatles Film & TV MemorabiliaBeatles Novelty ItemsBeatles Paper ItemsBeatles AutographsBeatles Concert MemorabiliaBeatles 1960s Posters & DisplaysBeatles Promotional Posters & DisplaysBeatles & Solo PhotographsBeatles Paper ItemsBeatles Magazines & Music PapersBob Wooler MemorabiliaBeatles Solo MemorabiliaJohn Lennon MemorabiliaPaul McCartney MemorabiliaGeorge Harrison Solo ItemsRingo Starr Solo ItemsVarious Artists MemorabiliaVarious ArtistsVarious Artists AutographsVarious Artists Tickets & PassesVarious Artists HandbillsVarious Artists ProgrammesVarious Artists PhotographsVarious Artists PostersVarious Artists RecordsVarious Artists Miscellaneous ItemsRolling StonesRolling Stones AutographsRolling Stones Concert TicketsRolling Stones HandbillsRolling Stones ProgrammesRolling Stones PhotographsVarious Rolling Stones MemorabiliaLed ZeppelinLed Zeppelin AutographsLed Zeppelin Concert MemorabiliaLed Zeppelin Various MemorabiliaJimi HendrixDavid BowieThe WhoQueenPunk ItemsContact Us
Login
Login
Close
